Swam Htet Aung

Full Stack Developer

- +959795865149
- Ubon Rachathani, Thailand
- **#** 08/08/2000
- Burmese
- in LinkedIn
- GitHub
- ▶ Portfolio



PROFILE

Passionate Web Developer with proficiency in a wide array of frontend and backend technologies. Able to effectively self manage during independent-projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. Also committed to delivering high-quality software solutions that enhance user experiences and drive business success.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

02/2024 – present Remote, Thailand

Befeni Limited

Full Stack Developer

- Develop web applications using PHP and it's frameworks like Laravel and Wordpress.
- Collaborating with team members on project planning and execution.
- Customizing WordPress themes and plugins.
- Ensuring code quality and adherence to best practices.
- Testing and debugging applications.
- Providing technical support and maintenance.

08/2023 – 01/2024 Yangon, Myanmar

Brycen Myanmar

Junior Web Developer

- -Actively engaged in ongoing skill improvement, exploring emerging technologies and best practices.
- -Implemented and maintained features using a combination of AngularJS and JAX-RS(Java).
- -Conducted thorough testing, including unit testing, to identify and address potential issues before deployment.

05/2023 - 07/2023

Brycen Myanmar

Yangon, Myanmar

Web Developer Intern

- Internship program focused in ReactJs and Laravel
- Built a full stack laravel project from scratch

07/2022 - 11/2022 Yangon, Myanmar **KBTC School of Information Technology**

Japanese lecturer

- Mainly teach Japanese N5 and N4 both in physical class and online class
- Determine study plan and prepare lecture slides

EDUCATION

07/2023 - Present

University of People

Computer Science

Enrolled in a Computer Science degree program through distance education, actively advancing academic knowledge to fuel future professional endeavors.

12/2016 - 01/2020

University of Information Technology

Yangon, Myanmar

Computer Science
Third Year Student

2011 - 2016

B.E.H.S (4) Hlaing

Yangon, Myanmar

Graduated

PROJECTS

06/2023 - 07/2023

Employee Registration System 2

A full stack web app for managing employee informations

- Independently led the entire project, managing it from start to finish.
- A full-fledged web application using Laravel for the backend and storing data in a MySQL database.
- Enhanced expertise in authentication, middleware implementation, and SQL through hands-on experience in the project's development.
- Actively participated in testing, creating comprehensive documentation, and ensuring the software met quality standards.

04/2023 - 06/2023

- Collaborated effectively with a local development team to contribute to a project, marking my initial experience working in a team environment.
- Implement User Friendly designs with ReactJs, Tailwind CSS and Mantine.

- Mainly worked in the Frontend part of the application
- Used MovieDB Api for backend data

05/2023 - Present

My Portfolio 🛮

- Implemented Next.js Server-Side Rendering and Search Engine Optimization techniques to optimize my personal portfolio for a seamless and user-friendly viewing experience.
- Utilized ReactJS and Tailwind CSS to design and style user interface components for optimal aesthetics and functionality.
- Implemented EmailJs in order to send an email to me directly from the website

LANGUAGES		
English	Burmese	
Japanese		
CERTIFICATES		

Responsive Web Design 🛮

freeCodeCamp

The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert! udemy

Basic Web Design / Special Web Design / Web Application Development MMSIT

Japanese N3

INTERESTS

Gaming

I love to play chill single player games in my free time to relax.

Sports

I am a fan of sports especially watching football.

Content Creation

Loves creating content on YouTube or Facebook about things I am interested.